<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<reviews version="1.0"><review><ID>41</ID><Name>Šeila</Name><Email>seila.becirovic@gmail.com</Email><Title>Mr. Robot</Title><Text>Mr. Robot: “Follows a young computer programmer who suffers from social anxiety disorder and forms connections through hacking. He's recruited by a mysterious anarchist, who calls himself Mr. Robot.”&#13;
Mr. Robot I started watching  because I saw that it ran after Suits, and I was curious to see what it’s about (USA network really does have some good shows). In the end trailer made up my mind along with the few reviews I had read. From episode one I fell in love with it. I found myself immersed in intriguing way the show was shot and produced. I honestly found it beautiful and I plan to watch Sam Esmail’s Comet as soon as I have the time. But above all let’s not forget the fact that the show is actually quite good and correct when it comes to technical aspects.&#13;
One thing I loved about both shows, which they have in common is the metaphors. Metaphors are probably my favorite figures of speech. And both shows know how to create a good metaphor. Every single episode, almost every single scene had either subtle or stronger hints of a different deeper meaning. Which left me a bit mind blown, especially after having spent some time analyzing it.&#13;
</Text><Pictures><Picture1>uploads/mrrobot_s2_cast_rami-malek2-2.jpg</Picture1><Picture2>uploads/mrrobot_s2_cast_portia-doubleday.jpg</Picture2><Picture3>uploads/mrrobot_s2_cast_carly-chaikin.jpg</Picture3></Pictures></review><review><ID>190</ID><Name>Šeila Bećirović</Name><Email>sbecirovic1@etf.unsa.ba</Email><Title>Hannibal</Title><Text>Hannibal:” Explores the early relationship between the renowned psychiatrist and his patient, a young FBI criminal profiler, who is haunted by his ability to empathize with serial killers.” &#13;
Hannibal has always been a source of fascination for me (Anthony Hopkins rules). I loved the movies, the books, and when I heard there was going to be a TV show I was genuinely excited, especially considering it was going to be directed by none other than Bryan Fuller. I could go on and on in praising the cast, storylines, but I find that unnecessary. The macabre of the show is just not that, macabre that is. It’s more an art show that consumes all your senses for thorough enjoyment. &#13;
Visual and audio aspects of the show is what beside other things drew me to it. Imagery is done up to a perfection. </Text><Pictures><Picture1>uploads/hannibal-ultra-hd-background_1_2560x1440.jpg</Picture1><Picture2>uploads/hannibal-gannibal-serial-uill-6257-1.jpg</Picture2><Picture3>uploads/download-1.jpg</Picture3></Pictures></review><review><ID>174</ID><Name>Anonymous</Name><Email>something.etwas@hotmail.com</Email><Title>Westworld</Title><Text>“Westworld” is television’s next big game-changer, a great, multilayered tapestry of action and unexpected analysis made hypnotic by creators Jonathan Nolan and Lisa Joy and a cast that includes Anthony Hopkins, Jeffrey Wright, James Marsden, Ed Harris, Thandie Newton and Evan Rachel Wood. It isn’t just great television, it’s vivid, thought-provoking television that entertains even as it examines the darker side of entertainment. &#13;
&#13;
“Westworld” is television’s next big game-changer, a great, multilayered tapestry of action and unexpected analysis made hypnotic by creators Jonathan Nolan and Lisa Joy and a cast that includes Anthony Hopkins, Jeffrey Wright, James Marsden, Ed Harris, Thandie Newton and Evan Rachel Wood. It isn’t just great television, it’s vivid, thought-provoking television that entertains even as it examines the darker side of entertainment.</Text><Pictures><Picture1>uploads/ZZ53B761E4-1.jpg</Picture1><Picture2>uploads/evan-rachel-wood-2560x1440-westworld-hd-4k-2519-1.jpg</Picture2><Picture3>uploads/hLVjGxw-1.png</Picture3></Pictures></review></reviews>
